var myQuestions = [
	{
		question: "Which of the following is invalid?",
		answers: {
			a: '_a = 1',
			b: '__a = 1',
			c: '__str__ = 1',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
	{
		question: " Which of the following is an invalid variable?",
		answers: {
			a: 'my_string_1',
			b: '1st_string',
			c: 'foo',
                        d: '_'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
		answers: {
			a: 'yes',
			b: 'no',
			c: 'machine dependent',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
		answers: {
			a: 'abc = 1,000,000',
			b: 'a b c = 1000 2000 3000',
			c: 'a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000',
                        d: 'a_b_c = 1,000,000'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Which is the correct operator for power(xy)?",
		answers: {
			a: 'X^y',
			b: 'X**y',
			c: 'X^^y',
            d: 'None of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "Which one of these is floor division?",
		answers: {
			a: '/',
			b: '//',
			c: '%',
                        d: 'none of the mentioned'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
{
		question: "In order to store values in terms of key and value we use what core data type.",
		answers: {
			a: 'list',
			b: 'tuple',
			c: 'class',
                        d: 'dictionary'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	},
{
		question: "What will be the output of the following Python code?<br>>>>str="+'"hello"'+"<br>>>>str[:2]",
		answers: {
			a: 'he',
			b: 'lo',
			c: 'olleh',
                        d: 'hello'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "What does ~4 evaluate to?",
		answers: {
			a: '-5',
			b: '-4',
			c: '-3',
                        d: '+3'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
{
		question: "What does 3 ^ 4 evaluate to?",
		answers: {
			a: '81',
			b: '12',
			c: '0.75',
                        d: '7'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'd'
	}
];